<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Jim Writes</title>
    <link>http://jimwrites.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Jim Writes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://jimwrites.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Fiio BTR5 Bluetooth Portable Headphone Amplifier</title>
      <link>http://jimwrites.com/post/2021-01-10-fiio-btr5/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jimwrites.com/post/2021-01-10-fiio-btr5/</guid>
      <description>This little portable amp puts out an incredible amount of power when you consider the size and cost. (about $100) It&amp;rsquo;s great to use for both IEMS or over ear headphones when you need to cut the cable from your source.</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Acer ET430K 43 inch monitor</title>
      <link>http://jimwrites.com/post/2020-08-18-acer-et430k-43-inch-monitor/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jimwrites.com/post/2020-08-18-acer-et430k-43-inch-monitor/</guid>
      <description>I writing this while looking at a ridiculously large 43 inch monitor. The monitor I have is the Acer ET430K but it looks like it&amp;rsquo;s been discontinued which is too bad because I only paid $350.00 for a refurbished model and I have had it for close to 2 years now and have had zero problems with it - it&amp;rsquo;s been great. I think I would be able to live without a monitor this size, but it&amp;rsquo;s fun.</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Assorted HDMI Cables</title>
      <link>http://jimwrites.com/post/2020-08-18-hmdi-cable/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jimwrites.com/post/2020-08-18-hmdi-cable/</guid>
      <description>I have multiples of this item from various manufacturers and makes and I can tell you that I don&amp;rsquo;t notice one bit of performance difference between any of them so my advice is to just get a well made cable like the AmazonBasics HDMI Cable and be done.</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Bic Round Stic Pen Blue Medium</title>
      <link>http://jimwrites.com/post/2020-08-18-bic-round-stic-ballpoint-pen-blue-medium/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jimwrites.com/post/2020-08-18-bic-round-stic-ballpoint-pen-blue-medium/</guid>
      <description>If I had to pick one pen it would be these. Bic Round Stic Blue Medium Pens. They are cheap at about five bucks a box and even though I am apt to lose pens I find a box of these last me for a pretty long time. I know there are those that are pen collectors but I just don&amp;rsquo;t get it as I rarely do any actual writing any more and these do the trick just fine for pennies each.</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Lenovo USA Lenovo ThinkPad USB-C Dock Gen 2 (40AS0090US)</title>
      <link>http://jimwrites.com/post/2020-08-18-lenovo-thinkpad-usbc-dock/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jimwrites.com/post/2020-08-18-lenovo-thinkpad-usbc-dock/</guid>
      <description>I bought this so I could hook my external monitors and peripherals to my Google Pixelbook and save me from plugging/unplugging a sea of cables as this allows me to use just one cable to connect to all my devices. This same cable also acts as a charger too so there&amp;rsquo;s even less worry. I paid nowhere the $150 price so I suggest you look for a used one if you can.</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Office Trash Can</title>
      <link>http://jimwrites.com/post/2020-08-18-trash-can/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jimwrites.com/post/2020-08-18-trash-can/</guid>
      <description>I think every home office has one of these and I am no exception. You need some place to toss your junk and this would do the trick. I&amp;rsquo;m surprised at how much these cost as $15.00 plus seems a lot for what it is but I&amp;rsquo;m not really up on prices for trash cans so maybe that&amp;rsquo;s how much they cost.</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Pen Cup</title>
      <link>http://jimwrites.com/post/2020-08-18-pen-cup/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jimwrites.com/post/2020-08-18-pen-cup/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s a cup that hold pens. There&amp;rsquo;s not much more to say about this. The one I have is a little fancier than this one actually but it does the same thing - holds pens. I have found that these can be a PITA because you end up tossing memory cards and thumb drives and other small things in there and then you have to remove all the pens to fish them out.</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Precision Hobby Knife</title>
      <link>http://jimwrites.com/post/2020-08-18-precision-hobby-knife/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jimwrites.com/post/2020-08-18-precision-hobby-knife/</guid>
      <description>I didn&amp;rsquo;t even know I had this! I guess this is more for use for crafters and the like and I rarely have a use for it so I might just toss this too in my effort to get rid of some stuff. If you do need one of these they are only about $7.00.</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Precision Screwdriver Kit</title>
      <link>http://jimwrites.com/post/2020-08-18-precision-screwdriver-kit/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jimwrites.com/post/2020-08-18-precision-screwdriver-kit/</guid>
      <description>I have better precision screwdrivers now so I think that this will get tossed as I no longer have a use for it. But for six bucks if you need a small set of screwdrivers you could do worse. I have used these for a good ten years and they have never failed me. My big problem is they get lost or misplaced over time, but you might have better luck.</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Seven Year Pen - Need Coffee</title>
      <link>http://jimwrites.com/post/2020-08-18-7-year-pen-need-coffee/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jimwrites.com/post/2020-08-18-7-year-pen-need-coffee/</guid>
      <description>I haven&amp;rsquo;t had this pen for 7 years yet so I will have to get back to you when it comes to whether it lasts the 7 years but I am surprised that they sell for over $12.00. For a pen! This was a gift so I wasn&amp;rsquo;t aware of the cost but I had better get at least 7 years out of it. That&amp;rsquo;s almost 2 dollars a year for a pen.</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Sharpie Pen</title>
      <link>http://jimwrites.com/post/2020-08-18-sharpiepen/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jimwrites.com/post/2020-08-18-sharpiepen/</guid>
      <description>The Sharpie Pen is not really my preference for a pen as I prefer a ball point but if you need a small fine sharpie then this is the one. They seem kind of pricey for what they are so this is one more thing that&amp;rsquo;s not getting replaced any time soon.</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Stabilo Write 4 All</title>
      <link>http://jimwrites.com/post/2020-08-18-write4all/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jimwrites.com/post/2020-08-18-write4all/</guid>
      <description>I think I bought this for when I was burning CD&amp;rsquo;s and I needed a marker for writing the song or album info. Of course, those days are long gone with spotify and the like so this isn&amp;rsquo;t really needed and I doubt it will get replaced. They cost about $1.50 each.</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Amazon Kindle Fire 7</title>
      <link>http://jimwrites.com/post/2020-08-17-amazon-fire-hd-7-tablet/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jimwrites.com/post/2020-08-17-amazon-fire-hd-7-tablet/</guid>
      <description>I bought this last holiday season for under $30.00, and when you think about it that&amp;rsquo;s an insane price for a tablet - any tablet - regardless of quality or features. This ended up being my little one&amp;rsquo;s tablet as I threw a [kid proof case])https://amzn.to/2YbYYpE) on it and then I really don&amp;rsquo;t have to worry about it. It&amp;rsquo;s not the greatest tablet but for the price one can&amp;rsquo;t complain. I&amp;rsquo;ve used it as a music player, ereader, TV for entertaining the kiddo and for light web browsing.</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Beyerdynamic DT 990 Pro Headphone</title>
      <link>http://jimwrites.com/post/2020-08-17-beyerdynamic-dt990-headphones/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jimwrites.com/post/2020-08-17-beyerdynamic-dt990-headphones/</guid>
      <description>These headphones were purchased with an Amazon Gift Card I was given at Christmas this past year and so I chose to spend it on these headphones. It&amp;rsquo;s been said that these are a very bright sounding headphone and I have to agree - But, because I am older and can&amp;rsquo;t hear the high frequencies anwyway these don&amp;rsquo;t bother me. I think I paid about $120.00 for them which I think is a great price for these.</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Large Gaming Mat for Keyboard and Mouse</title>
      <link>http://jimwrites.com/post/2020-08-17-large-gaming-mouse-pad/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jimwrites.com/post/2020-08-17-large-gaming-mouse-pad/</guid>
      <description>I bought two of these for about $10.00 each but I think I could have saved ten bucks and just bought one because I have retired one of them due to lack of use. Anyway it&amp;rsquo;s a big honking mouse pad that covers a big part of your desk. I bought them so that I would not have to set my pricey headphones down on my hard desk and at least there would be a little padding.</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Motorola Moto G Power Case</title>
      <link>http://jimwrites.com/post/2020-08-17-moto-g-power-case/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jimwrites.com/post/2020-08-17-moto-g-power-case/</guid>
      <description>I had to buy a new phone recently, and I decided on the Motorola Moto G Power as it was relatively cheap and I just needed a phone for a month or two until the phone I wanted was released later this summer. So I just picked a cheap case for my phone as I wasn&amp;rsquo;t planning on keeping it long</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Ultralink Optical Cables</title>
      <link>http://jimwrites.com/post/2020-08-17-optical-cable/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jimwrites.com/post/2020-08-17-optical-cable/</guid>
      <description>There was a time I was one of those &amp;ldquo;cables make a difference in sound&amp;rdquo;. No, they don&amp;rsquo;t. Although I bought some fancy optical cable doesn&amp;rsquo;t mean you should and just buy the Amazon Basics one at about 7 bucks if you need one. Save your money for what matters.</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Amazon Fire HD 10 2017</title>
      <link>http://jimwrites.com/post/2020-08-16-fire-hd-10-tablet/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jimwrites.com/post/2020-08-16-fire-hd-10-tablet/</guid>
      <description>I was given a hundred dollar Amazon gift card a few years back so I picked up this tablet. It&amp;rsquo;s ..fine. It&amp;rsquo;s no iPad, but it was on sale for $100 when I bought it so it costs a third of the price. It&amp;rsquo;s not the fastest and you&amp;rsquo;re limited to the Amazon ecosystem unless you hack it but for the price and what you do using tablet, it&amp;rsquo;s great for my uses a kindle reader, spotify remote or music player - and for a music player it sounds really great for the price.</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Dell P2317h Professional 23 inch Monitor</title>
      <link>http://jimwrites.com/post/2020-08-16-dell-2317h-professional-monitor/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jimwrites.com/post/2020-08-16-dell-2317h-professional-monitor/</guid>
      <description>In addtion to my Asus monitor I also use this Dell monitor too as a secondary monitor. Currently I use it mostly as a big baby monitor so I can keep an eye on the little one while she&amp;rsquo;s in bed. These sell new for about $250.00 but I paid much, much less. I bought these as a pair used, but one got broken during shipping so I ended up keeping the good monitor an only paying the $20.</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>HDMI Splitter</title>
      <link>http://jimwrites.com/post/2020-08-16-hdmi-splitter-adapter/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jimwrites.com/post/2020-08-16-hdmi-splitter-adapter/</guid>
      <description>This was one of those things that I had bought, but never got around to using until now when I added a 2nd computer to my system (My wife bought a new Mac Mini) and I didn&amp;rsquo;t have a dedicated monitor for it. So, I hooked my daily driver monitor up to this and my laptop and now I can switch beetween the Mac Mini and the Google PixelBook I use with ease.</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Paradigm CC-70 Center Channel Speaker</title>
      <link>http://jimwrites.com/post/2020-08-16-paradigm-cc-70-center-speaker/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jimwrites.com/post/2020-08-16-paradigm-cc-70-center-speaker/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m writing this from my little man cave in the corner of our basement and I mostly listen to headphones because: sleeping toddlers. But sometimes I fire up my old home theater receiver and play some music for speakers.
I use this as a very near near field speaker so I can keep the volume down. These are pretty cheap if you can find one used, but expect to pay about $200 for something that&amp;rsquo;s newer yet similar in specifications.</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>USB A to C cable</title>
      <link>http://jimwrites.com/post/2020-08-16-usb-to-usbc-cable/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jimwrites.com/post/2020-08-16-usb-to-usbc-cable/</guid>
      <description>About ten bucks for two of these seems to be the [going price] and for their use - they are fine. I use these for charging the phone in the car and I have a pair of shorter six inch ones for using to hook up my phone to battery chargers when I forget to charge my phone.</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>1/8 3.5mm to dual RCA Adapter</title>
      <link>http://jimwrites.com/post/2020-08-15-18-to-rca-male-cable/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jimwrites.com/post/2020-08-15-18-to-rca-male-cable/</guid>
      <description>Another cable in my neverending cable box, and this time it&amp;rsquo;s a 1/8 to 2 Male RCA cable that is used to hookup things that have a headphone jack like your phone or computer to your home stereo or other device that has rca inputs. Currently I am using one to connect a DAC to a headphone amplifier. These are only about $10.00.</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>1/8 to 1/8 Aux Cable</title>
      <link>http://jimwrites.com/post/2020-08-15-aux-cable/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jimwrites.com/post/2020-08-15-aux-cable/</guid>
      <description>The last cable I am writing about for today (don&amp;rsquo;t worry, there&amp;rsquo;s more) is a 1/8 to 1/8 aux cable. This is another cable to have in your junk drawer for just in case times. I know bluetooth is king these days but for those of us without bluetooth but with an AUX input, this cable allows us to connect our phones to the car stereo and makes the drive more bearable.</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Asus VS239-H 23 inch IPS Monitor</title>
      <link>http://jimwrites.com/post/2020-08-15-asus-23-inch-monitor/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jimwrites.com/post/2020-08-15-asus-23-inch-monitor/</guid>
      <description>I researched and researched for a cheap IPS monitor and this one fit the bill. It&amp;rsquo;s big enough, bright enough and sharp enough. I&amp;rsquo;m not a gamer so the other stuff doesn&amp;rsquo;t really matter like refresh rate. For general computer use you could do worse. Priced at about $120.00</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Monolith Liquid Spark Headphone Amplifier</title>
      <link>http://jimwrites.com/post/2020-08-15-monolith-liquid-spark-headphone-amplifier/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jimwrites.com/post/2020-08-15-monolith-liquid-spark-headphone-amplifier/</guid>
      <description>The Monolith Liquid Spark Headphone Amplifier is really all the headphone amplifier you really need as it&amp;rsquo;s powerful enough and quiet enough. The volume knob is one of the best feeling knobs on an amp I have heard and it&amp;rsquo;s well built. These sell for about $110.00 new but used ones pop up all the time on Amazon for much less.</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Monster RCA Cables</title>
      <link>http://jimwrites.com/post/2020-08-15-monster-rca-cable/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jimwrites.com/post/2020-08-15-monster-rca-cable/</guid>
      <description>Don&amp;rsquo;t get sucked into the monster brand like I did and just buy these instead. These Amazon Basics RCA CAbles are cheap at about 10.00 and do the job just fine. Save your money on fancy cables and buy music instead.</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Audio CB-1 Over the Ear Headphones</title>
      <link>http://jimwrites.com/post/2020-08-15-status-audio-cb-1-headphones/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jimwrites.com/post/2020-08-15-status-audio-cb-1-headphones/</guid>
      <description>I needed a pair of closed-back over ear headphones and these were cheap enough and got good reviews so here they are. They are fine. These are the headphones I use when I don&amp;rsquo;t want to be disturbed or disturb others with my music or movies. My only complaint with these is that they feel more like on-ears on my big head and they are not the most comfortable headphone I have ever bought.</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Topping D10 USB DAC</title>
      <link>http://jimwrites.com/post/2020-08-15-topping-d10-dac/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jimwrites.com/post/2020-08-15-topping-d10-dac/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve gone through a few DACs and if was being completly honest they all sound just about the same. I like this particular one though as it has both optical and COAX out in addtion to RCA. This allows me to use 2 amplifiers with just one DAC. This DAC sells for about $80.00 new.</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>USB A male to USB micro b cable</title>
      <link>http://jimwrites.com/post/2020-08-15-micro-usb-charging-cable/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jimwrites.com/post/2020-08-15-micro-usb-charging-cable/</guid>
      <description>I have an entire drawer full of these in certain lengths and manufacturers and yet I can&amp;rsquo;t get rid of them yet as in this day and age not all my devices have gone to USB-C so I can&amp;rsquo;t pitch these yet. Off the top of my head, I know my Amazon Fire Tablets still use this cable for charging. It&amp;rsquo;s a good thing this cable is cheap at about $7.</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>USB A to USB Cable</title>
      <link>http://jimwrites.com/post/2020-08-15-usb-a-usb-B-cable/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jimwrites.com/post/2020-08-15-usb-a-usb-B-cable/</guid>
      <description>I know for a fact that I have more than one of these in a drawer because you never know when you need one of these to hook up some peripheral to your computer. These cables are commonly used to connect a printer via USB but some peripherals use this cable too like my Topping D10 DAC. Price is about $7.00 for these.</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>16 foot tape measure</title>
      <link>http://jimwrites.com/post/2020-08-14-16-foot-tape-measure/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jimwrites.com/post/2020-08-14-16-foot-tape-measure/</guid>
      <description>Sometimes you can cheap out and just buy whatever from the dollar store but I find that it&amp;rsquo;s worth the while to spend the money on good tools as they save so much time and frustration than some crappy thing. An example is I bought a cheap tape measure and it broke on the very first use! I had to throw it out and just cough up the money for the brand name one.</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Anker Astro E1 battery pack</title>
      <link>http://jimwrites.com/post/2020-08-14-anker-e1-battery-charger/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jimwrites.com/post/2020-08-14-anker-e1-battery-charger/</guid>
      <description>This charger has a story. I bought this three days before my daughter was born and I knew that I did not want to worry about having enough power or finding a wall plug at the hospital so instead of keeping my phone charged I kept this charger topped up instead and used it to charge my phone. This was probably the best purchase I made in 2019. It&amp;rsquo;s almost 2 years later and it&amp;rsquo;s still going strong.</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Chicco Mini Bravo Plus Lightweight Stroller</title>
      <link>http://jimwrites.com/post/2020-08-14-chico-lightweight-stroller/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jimwrites.com/post/2020-08-14-chico-lightweight-stroller/</guid>
      <description>I use this stroller daily so it&amp;rsquo;s earned it&amp;rsquo;s worth (about $180.00) as it keeps the little one entertained for the hour we are out for a walk and folks you can&amp;rsquo;t put money on an entertained toddler.
The buckles are a little fiddly until you get used them and this thing rolls much better with a squirt of wd-40 on the wheels. It&amp;rsquo;s been over a year since we&amp;rsquo;ve had this stroller and so far so good.</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Hydraulic Monitor Arm</title>
      <link>http://jimwrites.com/post/2020-08-14-monitor-arm/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jimwrites.com/post/2020-08-14-monitor-arm/</guid>
      <description>I think one of the best things you can do for yourself is to make sure your computer station or desk is as ergonomic as possible and one way to do this is to replace the stand you have with a monitor arm you can adjust.
I have one that allows me to have a 2nd monitor off to my right while I use my main monitor for the big work.</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>USA Baseball Cap</title>
      <link>http://jimwrites.com/post/2020-08-14-usa-baseball-cap/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jimwrites.com/post/2020-08-14-usa-baseball-cap/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been in the habit lately of grabbing a ball cap as I go out the door. This is something I never did when younger, but the hat now keeps my bald spot from burnin and allows me some protection of my eyes from the sun thanks to the brim. It&amp;rsquo;s not for fashion but for function so I really don&amp;rsquo;t care about logos and the like but my current daily driver is like the one you see here.</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>LK Phone Screen Protectors</title>
      <link>http://jimwrites.com/post/2020-08-13-lk-screen-protectors/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jimwrites.com/post/2020-08-13-lk-screen-protectors/</guid>
      <description>I found this brand of screen protectors for my Google Pixel 3A and I like them. You get three of them, so you have a couple of chances to get it right and straight which is a problem when you try to install these things.
They are glass and don&amp;rsquo;t seem to harm the display or what you see and seem to be optically clear. I also like that these offer a nicer feel to the glass than whatever the stock glass is on phones as it feels smoother to me and makes it easier to scroll with your thumb.</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Logitech M317c Wireless Mouse</title>
      <link>http://jimwrites.com/post/2020-08-13-logitech-md317c-wireless-mouse/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jimwrites.com/post/2020-08-13-logitech-md317c-wireless-mouse/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m a fan of Logitech Mice. They work well for me and it&amp;rsquo;s all I need. I have tried some other mice like the Amazon Basics Mouse and they are okay but not great.
I have tried all kinds of mice: Apple Mice, Gaming Mice and I have probably spent hundreds of dollars on different input devices but the logitech mice work the best for me it seems and they are cheap at about $20.</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>marimekko notepad collection</title>
      <link>http://jimwrites.com/post/2020-08-13-marimekko-notepad/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jimwrites.com/post/2020-08-13-marimekko-notepad/</guid>
      <description>I have no idea where these notepads came from but the other day my wife gave me this as I was looking for a notepad and this is what I was given so this is what gets used. I know some of you hipsters are fond of moleskine notebooks but I&amp;rsquo;m not that cool and a back of an envelope will do for me most times.</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>MOSISO Universal Headphone Hanger</title>
      <link>http://jimwrites.com/post/2020-08-13-headphone-hanger/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jimwrites.com/post/2020-08-13-headphone-hanger/</guid>
      <description>I have a few of these headphone hangers and I guess you could say I like them as I have more than one of them. They&amp;rsquo;re simple and clamp to almost any desk I have tried with them and then you can plunk the headphones on the hangers and then swing them under the desk out of the way.
I think this is a great thing because I have found the less cables you have on your desktop the less chance of spilling your coffee all over your electronics.</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Office Scissors</title>
      <link>http://jimwrites.com/post/2020-08-13-office-scissors/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jimwrites.com/post/2020-08-13-office-scissors/</guid>
      <description>Another item I don&amp;rsquo;t know where or how they got here but there you go. I think it&amp;rsquo;s good to have a few pair of scissors and for about $10 for 3 pair you can&amp;rsquo;t really go wrong with these amazon basics ones.</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>One Small Paperclip</title>
      <link>http://jimwrites.com/post/2020-08-13-one-small-paperclip/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jimwrites.com/post/2020-08-13-one-small-paperclip/</guid>
      <description>I think I have had the same box of 1000 paperclips for over 20 years now and I still have the same box. What can I write about a paperclip? It&amp;rsquo;s..a paperclip. They are good for other uses than the intended though and I have used them for everything from sim card ejectors for phones to just keeping something secure and sometimes a paperclip is the very first thing I try.</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Airtight Coffee Cannister</title>
      <link>http://jimwrites.com/post/2021-02-23-airtight-coffee-tin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jimwrites.com/post/2021-02-23-airtight-coffee-tin/</guid>
      <description>For reasons I am not quite sure the wife has decided that we needed to start drinking fancy coffee and the store brand stuff was no good. The problem was that the store brand stuff came in it&amp;rsquo;s own tin which was large-mouthed and it was really easy to dig the coffee out ih the morning. The bags that this coffee comes in is hard to manage with the scoop without getting more coffee on the counter than in the french press.</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Sanford HB 2 Wood Pencil</title>
      <link>http://jimwrites.com/post/2021-02-23-sampson-hb2-pencil/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jimwrites.com/post/2021-02-23-sampson-hb2-pencil/</guid>
      <description>Like a lot of stuff in my drawers at home I have no idea where I got this pencil, but here you go. I don&amp;rsquo;t have much use for a pencil in my everyday but once in a while it&amp;rsquo;s nice to have a few around the house. I find I mostly use it when I need to mark where I will cut some wood or make a hole in the wall.</description>
    </item>
    
    
  </channel>
</rss>
